Your hands lie open in the long fresh grass.
The finger points look through like rosy blooms.
Your eyes smile peace.
The pasture gleams and glooms
beneath billowing skies that scatter and amass.
All round our nest far as the eye can pass.
Our golden king cup feels with silver edge
where the cow partially skirts the Hawthorn hedge
to his visible silence still is the hourglass.
Your hands lie open in the long fresh grass.
The finger points look through like rosy blooms.
Your eyes smile peace.
The pasture gleams and glooms
beneath billowing skies that scatter and amass.
All round our nest far as the eye can pass.
Our golden king cup feels with silver edge
where the cow partially skirts the Hawthorn hedge
to his visible silence still is the hourglass.